interface Subtraction {
    id: number;
    question: string;
    answer: number;
  }
  
  const subtractions: Subtraction[] = [
    { id: 1, question: '10 - 4', answer: 6 },
    { id: 2, question: '8 - 3', answer: 5 },
    { id: 3, question: '15 - 7', answer: 8 },
    { id: 4, question: '20 - 9', answer: 11 },
    { id: 5, question: '14 - 6', answer: 8 },
    { id: 6, question: '30 - 15', answer: 15 },
    { id: 7, question: '25 - 10', answer: 15 },
    { id: 8, question: '12 - 5', answer: 7 },
    { id: 9, question: '18 - 9', answer: 9 },
    { id: 10, question: '7 - 2', answer: 5 },
    { id: 11, question: '22 - 8', answer: 14 },
    { id: 12, question: '16 - 4', answer: 12 },
    { id: 13, question: '13 - 6', answer: 7 },
    { id: 14, question: '9 - 3', answer: 6 },
    { id: 15, question: '11 - 7', answer: 4 },
    { id: 16, question: '19 - 8', answer: 11 },
    { id: 17, question: '28 - 12', answer: 16 },
    { id: 18, question: '35 - 20', answer: 15 },
    { id: 19, question: '40 - 15', answer: 25 },
    { id: 20, question: '26 - 11', answer: 15 },
    { id: 21, question: '17 - 9', answer: 8 },
    { id: 22, question: '23 - 14', answer: 9 },
    { id: 23, question: '32 - 18', answer: 14 },
    { id: 24, question: '21 - 13', answer: 8 },
    { id: 25, question: '27 - 17', answer: 10 },
    { id: 26, question: '33 - 26', answer: 7 },
    { id: 27, question: '38 - 29', answer: 9 },
    { id: 28, question: '45 - 36', answer: 9 },
    { id: 29, question: '50 - 43', answer: 7 },
    { id: 30, question: '47 - 39', answer: 8 },
  ];
  
  export default subtractions;
  